

# João Areias

I'm a 26-year-old computer engineer with some professional experience, but with a great desire to gain new skills and embrace new challenges and continue to evolve as a professional. I'm passionate about technology and want to expand my knowledge in the field. I have no problem communicating and I have no problem leaving my comfort zone.

#### Contact

911586322



joaoareias11@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/joao areias/

#### Skills

**Creative Thinking** 

**Emotions Control** 

**Teamwork** 

**WEB Development** 

**Javascript** 

PHP

Agile

MySQL

**AngularJS** 

**ReactJS** 

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

Redux

**Typescript** 

Node.js

GIT

C#

Java

**ASP.NET** 

**MongoDB** 

Docker

#### Experience

Experience gained in work done for assessment purposes during my undergraduate and master's degrees. Experience in group work using the SCRUM methodology.

#### Consultant SI | ITSECTOR | 2023 - Actual - 1 Year 8 Months

As part of a team developing specific applications for a particular client.

Technologies: Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Agile

### Junior WEB Developer | E-GOI | 2022 - 2023 - 1 Year 1 Month

As part of a web development team, but I end up working with a bit of everything.

Technologies: Javascript, PHP, AngularJS, Docker, CSS, HTML, Typescript, MySQL, Svelte

## Project/Internship | E-GOI | 2021 - 2022 - 5 Months

Development of a new communication channel to be integrated into the E-goi product.

Technologies: Javascript, PHP, AngularJS, Docker, CSS, HTML, Typescript, MySQL

#### Project/Internship | INOVA+ | 2020 - 5 Months

Development of a platform based on the Open Source FarmBot solution for analyzing agricultural crops. Redesign of the existing FarmBot application and improvements.

Technologies: React, Ruby, TypeScript, Docker, CSS, VirtualBox, HTML.

#### Languages

Portuguese | English | Spanish

# Education

12th Year of Schooling with the Science and Technology Course | Mirandela | 2013 - 2016

Degree in computer engineering | ISEP | 2016 - 2020

Master's in software engineering | ISEP | 2020 - 2022

# Licenses and Certificates

Agile Advanced Professional Training | SCOPPHU | 2022 - https://drive.google.com/file/d/1SWFmp7vIkeRu\_-ljDfvKIF7SLt3RKkAH/view?usp=sharing